elections.ab.ca 2018-06-09

# Privacy & Security | Elections Alberta

Elections Alberta is committed to providing our visitors with a web site that respects their privacy. This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices on our web site.

We do not automatically gather any personal information from you, such as your name, phone number, e-mail or address. This information is only obtained if you supply it voluntarily, usually through contacting us via e-mail, or registering in a secure portion of the site.

Any personal information you do provide is managed according to statute. This means that, at the point of collection, you will be informed that your personal information is being collected, the purpose for which it is being collected and that you have the right of access to the information.

This web site does not use “cookies” or any other means of collecting information about you or your computer without your knowledge. (A “cookie” is a file placed on your hard drive by a web site that allows the web site to monitor your use of the site, usually without your knowledge). However, we do use a software program to monitor network traffic to gather statistical information on web site usage. This software receives and records the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer that has contacted our web site, the date and time of the visit and the pages visited. We make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting our site.

This web site contains links to other sites, including other government agencies. We are not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other web sites and encourage you to examine each site’s privacy policy and disclaimers and make your own decisions regarding the privacy of those sites and the accuracy and reliability of material and information found.

Information at this site is provided solely for the user’s information and, while thought to be accurate, is provided strictly “as is” and without warranty of any kind, whether express or implied. The Crown, its agents, employees, or contractors will not be liable to you for any damages, direct or indirect, or lost profits or data arising out of your use of information provided at this site, or information provided at any other site that can be accessed from this site. Proceeding beyond this disclaimer constitutes acceptance of these terms and conditions. For inquiries please [contact Elections Alberta](http://www.elections.ab.ca/contact-us/).

View Government of Alberta’s Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy ([FOIP](http://www.servicealberta.ca/foip/)) Act.
